Kiss and Cry is a romance, drama, music film directed by Sean Cisterna.
A romantic drama based on the story of Carley Allison, a promising 18 year old figure skater and singer
who made medical history in her fight against a rare 1 in 3.5 billion type of sarcoma.
Carley Allison, played by Sarah Fisher.
John Servinis, played by Luke Bilyk.
May Allison, played by Chantal Kreviazuk.
Mark Allison, played by Sergio Di Zio.
Rebecca, played by Zoë Belkin.
Riley Allison, played by Brittany Bristow.
Kiss and Cry is a 2017 Canadian biopic directed by Sean Cisterna.
The film depicts the life of Carley Allison who
suffered from a rare form of cancer.
It was filmed at various real locations, such as Carley’s house and
bedroom, skating rink, classrooms and hospitals in Toronto.
The film stars Carley’s real-life friend Sarah Fisher.
Throughout the film, Fisher breaks the fourth wall, using the very words
from the real Allison’s blog posts and You Tube performances.
The letter Carley writes and addresses to “cancer”
is also partly her actual words.
It was released on February 10, 2017 and has been rated as a 6.8 out of 10.
The film explores themes of cancer, figure
skating, teenage girl, woman director.
The tone is emotional.